Huh!
Grandma!
Aah!
Did you ever make it into a manicure?
She has.
Should we have a little dance here or something?
Yeah, sure.
Goochiko step.
I'm doing it.
Mum's doing the goo choo choo step.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Honestly, I don't want to go home.
It's a rough car.
The driver's about 50... 500? [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward]
Oh, here they come!
Sorry I'm late.
Your car is here.
Let's go.
[fast forward]
Oh, is this okay? The big one?
Oh, wait, what? Is that okay? The big one?
Oh, wait. I think we should take a cutaway shot, like I'm going shopping.
I don't know which one I should do... all the time.
Just in case you're the girl who eats the whole thing when it comes.
Do you want some of this cream? Always... a woman who eats a round when she comes...
This cream.
Want some?
This one.
You chose this one? This one's better.
Why do you only have a light bite?
Oh, no, no, no, this one's better.
What the hell does that mean?
What?
Tell me what it means.
This one's a bit more...
It's melting. How many times have I told you, this one's starting to melt a bit more.
Additional liquid.
Make it the same.
Ta-da!
No, I mean...
Okay, ladies and gentlemen.
It's time to make the cake.
Yay.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow.
A big, big
There's a futon.
And look.
Three in a row.
Look.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Okay, then.
Now we're going to put the whipped cream on like this.
Put the whipped cream on top.
That's it.
Here you go.
There's a pinprick.
I gave it to you, Azu-san, in the new year! He's flying. Yuuka's flying too
What should you do?
The whipped cream's flying!
Hang in there!
Oh, wait.
I didn't put any sugar in it.
Grandma.
Sugar, sugar, sugar.
Oh, no, it's done.
There's still a lot of it.
I know, right?
Hmm.
Let's paint it together.
You can't paint with this.
Can I paint with this?
So, what does cake mean to you guys?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay, bye.
Yum!
Yeah, it is.
It's good.
It's fun.
Fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart, fart!
I don't want to say "fart", but I'm going to give you a ride.
Hurry up!
I want some whipped cream.
I can't.
No, I was doing that last.
That was the last time we did that.
Wait, wait, wait, I just did that.
Last one!
Okay, I'll just stick it out.
No. 2, No. 2.
No. 2, for now.
- I'll follow the blessing. There's something wrong with the cake.
There's too many of them.
Have you really ever made a cake?
He said he has.
I have.
Finish it.
Skip.
OK, OK, OK, OK.
Now we are making German potatoes.
My mother...
She only makes German potatoes.
She's the kind of mother who can't make much else.
I'm going to make this today, and I'm going to make something else, because my mum's the kind of mum who can't make much.
I'm going to make this today, and I'm going to make something else.
This is our family's secret recipe.
That's right.
Anyone can do it, honestly.
Oh, yes, really.
We make it in our house with Rahman potatoes called curry stew.
The rest is a vegetable casserole.
The other day my mum said it was her favourite roast, and we've got a dish that we put on the table.
Just do this for a minute. Yes, yes ... I was hedge-hodding home.
Yes, this is the father who sometimes folds over like a racket when he reads that familiar newspaper.
Yo, Marble.
Bon appétit!
Yes, ma'am.
I'll take it, Grandma.
Granny water
Pop.
Four or five.
Can you bring me some?
That's fine, thank you.
You don't always do that.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was going to put German fries in there.
I was going to put in some lovely potatoes!
Potato tart. Yum!
Thank you! It's so good! That's awesome.
This is my grandma's homemade oshizushi.
The guy who just came home from work is like my brother.
Number one on the list of people who would definitely be in town.
Singer Song.
My two sisters are water polo girls.
Like the king of water polo.
Hey...
Who's Miwako Eien Festival?
Did we all play?
Yes! We did!
Everyone told me to shut up, shut up, shut up.
Miyako Eien...
They said I was going to die.
I did, didn't I?
How many hours did we do it for?
Three hours.
A little over three hours.
Oh, but that was...
That was really hard.
Oh, no, no, no.
Is it good?
Very tasty.
Aubergine is good too.
Aubergine is so good.
Aubergine is good.
Delicious.
This is Grandpa's aubergine.
Like these?
Grandpa's aubergine?
Yes, Grandpa makes them for me.
Well, then, why don't you guys go to your favourite place?
What? Go?
Yes, that's nice.
Yes...
It's at the top.
Yes, sir.
They make a nice camera.
Mm-hm.
What about you, Marvellous? No, I'm sure the camera will clean him up... That's a good connection.
The cow is white.
You can't choose.
I can't choose.
I can't pick one, so I'm doing my best.
Yay!
Have I told my mum yet?
I did.
I don't even remember telling her.
She says I'm number two.
What about tsundere number two?
Tsundere.
How about tsundere number two?
No.
No?
She's a tsundere, but she loves her family the most.
She does.
And the last one?
Last one's here.
Bon appétit.
I'm really serious about this.
Think of your family.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
That's great.
Excellent, everybody applaud.
Everybody clap, thank you.
That's wonderful.
Did I tell you, Naokäsan?
Yes, I did.
You're so eager to say it.
I forgot what I said.
Why don't you just say what you like about everyone?
No, no, why not?
What?
Why not?
What? You should say it.
I won't tell you, what should we do, have a little dance here or something? What? What? What? What? What? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Yes! We've done it!
Eleven, eleven, eleven.
It's the occasion of my birthday, so my mum's doing it for me.
Emergency birthday.
Oh, man, now I think about it.
So, which one do you guys want?
This is the only one now... This one! This is the one! Bon appétit!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Yum!
It's so good!
Delicious!
It's like something I've eaten before.
You're eating it!
You're eating it, aren't you?
After that, apple time awaits!
Our annual...
64.
Sixty-four.
Do you have any?
38.
Uh-oh.
Ooh.
Yay apples.
Yay!
This is how we choose our prizes!
5075 Yay! This is how we are choosing our prizes 175
I'm going home now.
I would be happy if I could bring you something like a normal conversation, the best.
Yeah, I mean, like, a normal conversation, like, too normal a conversation.
So, let's discuss why people sleep on futons?
I'd love to.
Yes...
No.
Oh, there it is.
Flash book. Oh, oh, oh.
He wants to move on.
Do it right.
He wants to move, he wants to move, he wants to move.
Guchko yes, Guchko yes.
I just went through this.
Look, mother, look, look!
Gutko step.
I'm doing it
Mother's gu-chi-co step ah-kan shite shite shite bunkei mother's bunkei gu-chi-co step
Bunkei ahaha
Akan, yes.
Akan Today's the second day.
Akan, yay Bunkei, ahaha, your mother and I are cooking a big family meal for all four of us.
I'd like to go shopping for it
Yay!
Let's go
I'm usually talking about a supermarket ladder.
Or maybe three shops...
And the Postcos that we all know and love.
I buy a lot, but I go there three times a week.
It's like Hostco is my hometown.
That's why we have a freezer at home.
Two freezers.
One and two.
It's been around for a long time, but it's...
It's been around for a long time.
But, you know, ice cream, too.
They only buy it in packs of 10.
They don't buy it for me.
A box of ice cream.
Even if you buy 10 boxes...
I only have about one box.
That's true, isn't it?
No more than two or three per person.
How many are supposed to be in each person's box?
Definitely one box.
Mum, speak louder.
No! She says no, no, no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no, she says no. Who's there?
Who's there? And she says, "Who?
Your mother says, "Shut up.
And then she shuts up.
They're all going to throw up.
Who's there?
Who is it? Like...
Maybe I thought it was someone who was talking.
And then...
They were measuring it in grams.
I might have been suspicious of the person who said the snacks were also scented, because they were measured in grams, and so were the snacks, and so were the snacks.
It's all about the smell, isn't it?
People fight over it.
Get a big bag.
With a scale.
Measure.
Calculate how many grams it contains.
How many people measure, how many grams.
Is there a small one?
I really do.
I miss it.
It's over there.
It's a bit too hot.
Taken.
Where'd you look?
I'm hit, I'm hit, I'm hit, I'm hit, I'm hit.
Is it over?
What's the end?
This is what we bought this time, and this is what we're having for dinner.
This is for dinner.
It's all gone in a jiffy.
Your amazing mother always puts down the bike explosively.
Yay!
Okay, we've got three games now, three people who are like younger brothers and sisters and stuff.
I'd like to cook dinner for all of them.
What are you making now?
I'm making vegetable soup.
My sister is cutting it for me.
Erin cut.
Erin.
Oh, no.
Okay, we're done.
What's an erin-kiri?
It's been cracking for a while now, from all of you.
You know how to cut an erin so it looks nice, don't you?
Do it.
This one, right?
I think they got the message.
I'd hate it if someone was this good.
Elingbullah! Like an Elingbara.
Oh, you're so abstract.
Can you see this?
But it's good.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
That's what I'm talking about.
You're really good at this.
Come to Unicuni, everyone!
Oh, no.
My mum says I can do it with a bell camera.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no! The muster!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, God, I've got to put my hand in there and stop it.
We've had a lot of muster fights in the house recently.
Siblings don't fight these days.
They're good friends.
Oh, yeah?
You've been going to the bathroom to stop them fighting, and there haven't been any fights between the three or four of you lately, because you get on so well and you're so alike.
You went to the bathroom to stop them fighting.
We've stopped three or four fights in the bathroom.
I went to the bathroom to tell Mommy to stop fighting.
In the bathroom, like, beep-beep-beep.
You'd be like a squid.
I miss those days.
Like a bleep bleep bleep.
That's right.
Then I'll just listen to the story and go home.
You tell them to stop.
And she says, "No, thank you.
Oh, that's what your mother would say.
There was one... I miss it.
I miss it.
I'm in my house now...
Ta-da!
Like this...
At the entrance...
There's a lot of Nao stuff here.
There's quite a lot of stuff from the radio.
There's a lot of stuff from the radio.
There's also some birth items.
I'm so happy.
It's very encouraging when my family supports me.
So, dinner is ready.
There's still a lot of bean sprouts in there.
There's still enough to do everything, but...
We're having yakiniku for dinner today, but it's a bit more affordable.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is the Inviti family's dinner.
Yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes.
We'll eat then.
No, thank you.
Sprouts! Ready, bean sprouts!
No, thank you!
I wish I could have eaten it with you.
Ha-ha-ha, I screwed up a bit.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Delicious.
It's good.
Yes, it is.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm scared.
This is scary... this is scary... this is scary...
a-ha-ha-ha-ha
This...
My sense of humor is a bit...
It's so shallow...
It's not good.
There's no more room for bean sprouts.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Helpers! Help, help, help, help!
Helpiker.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha, I'm coming to help! I'll go help!
No, no, no!
Rice on the booster!
Wait a minute, I'm putting food on the booster.
Subscribe to our channel! I feel like I'm about to eat.
What? - Yeah, I do.
I don't really want to go home or anything.
But if I tell you, you're gonna think it's so gross.
Right, I've stopped.
Honestly?
To be honest...
You honestly don't want to go home?
Yeah, I do.
Oh! You're back!
Oh! Who's there? I don't want to go home! I'm back!
Who's there?
I'm back!
But there's still one more to go.
I'm going to enjoy the evening.
Evening.
Please subscribe to our channel, rate us highly and comment!
Bye-bye!
Ta-da!
What is this?
What is this... a white, pure white liquid.
I wonder how this will turn out.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's getting a bit hard.
That's good.
From now on, from now on, grandma will make a fist.
Fist.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm already getting hard.
I'm always making mistakes here.
Once you put out the fire, you know.
Oh, Sen, you've done it with the fire on.
Probably.
Oh...
Are you tired?
I'm tired.
You want a change?
What's wrong?
Did I turn invisible?
It's transparent to everyone who sees it.
I don't know.
Is this cheap for a dual purpose?
This, this, this... would it be transparent if you looked at it?
I don't know.
I think it'll give you skinny arms.
What do you think? How's this?
It's at a really bad angle.
Angle.
Yeah, it's good.
It's so good, Grandma.
It's mellow.
And it's good with soybean flour, too.
Do you want some of Grandpa's?
Yes, yes, yes.
This one's good.
Only then.
Yes, it's good.
I'll take a picture of Grandpa.
What? I'll film you.